globaldirectmedia.com 2013-04-14

# Privacy | Unanimis

This policy was last updated on **18th April 2011**

If you have any questions, comments or suggestions about this privacy policy or the way in which Unanimis deals with your personal information, please contact us at:

or send a letter to:

Data Protection Officer,  
Unanimis Consulting Ltd, 17 Gresse Street, London, W1T 1QL

**Privacy Policy**  
Unanimis treats the privacy of personal information with the utmost seriousness as we realise that it is of great importance to our customers and internet users alike. The information displayed here demonstrates Unanimis’ commitment to protecting your privacy.

**Our Right to Change This Policy**  
Unanimis reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. We will let you know at the top of this page the date it was last updated.

This privacy policy covers all of the services offered by Unanimis Group Limited and its subsidiaries Unanimis Consulting Limited and m3 Media Services Limited. For simplicity, we will use “Unanimis” in this policy to refer to all these companies to make reading this policy easier. Our aim by publishing this privacy policy is to inform you of the kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit the Unanimis website or a website using Unanimis’ ad serving technology and services, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to limit the access to the information that we collect.

We have written this privacy policy with the intention of it being easy to understand and read. Some of the information about cookies and their use can be quite technical and we want you to be completely informed about how cookies work, and how we use information collected through the Internet.

## Information collected through the Unanimis website

**How do we use personal information that you provide to Unanimis through our website?**

**Information requests and inquiries**  
When you submit requests for information or inquiries through the Unanimis website, we will use the personal information you provide to deal with your request or inquiry.

This information may include contact details, such as name, address, and email address. The personal information we collect may change from time to time, but will only be collected when you give it voluntarily.

**Updates, new products/services and other related matters**  
With your consent, we may use your personal information to inform you of new services, changes to the Unanimis website and other related matters which we feel may be of interest to you.

Except as detailed below, you will not be automatically included in such mailings, but must actively request them, either when you provide your registration information or at a later time. We will not use your personal information to send you unsolicited marketing communications by email or otherwise without your consent.

We may use personal information obtained from you in the course of a sale or negotiations for the purchase of products or services to contact you and send you information regarding similar products or services, but we will always give you the opportunity to refuse any future use of your personal information in this way.

Unanimis will not intentionally disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent. However, you acknowledge that we may disclose to a third party where it is necessary to do so in order to deal with any request or inquiry you have made using the Unanimis website. We may also disclose your personal information to a third party in connection with any sale of the business of any Unanimis group company.

## Ad serving data collection general information

**Use of Cookies**  
To make advertising more relevant to users of the Internet, Unanimis uses a common Internet technology called “cookies.” Cookies are small and harmless packets of information that are placed on people’s computers when the computer browser views one of our client’s advertisements. A cookie is a bit like a sign saying, “This computer browser saw an ad”. It tells us the computer’s browser has at some point viewed one of our client’s advertisements. A cookie has no information in it that could identify you as an individual, such as your name, address, phone number, email address. It’s a random and anonymous number that we assign to that Internet browser on that computer just to tell us we’ve seen this browser at a site where one of our clients advertises. We assign a cookie to every user who visits a website where a Unanimis banner advertisement is displayed and where our web beacons (see discussion below) are placed. Many websites use cookies to help tailor web pages to the user’s unique needs and interests, based on either a user’s past actions when visiting a website, or based on ways a user has chosen to customize the website. Unanimis uses cookies solely to track advertising effectiveness and to select the best ads to serve. One example of this is measuring how often an anonymous user sees an ad; among other things this helps us ensure that the user is not shown the same ad over and over again.

**Platform for Privacy Preferences Project (P3P)**  
Unanimis complies with the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) P3P specifications Candidate Release for cookies used in serving advertisements on behalf of our clients. You can view the P3P specification at <http://www.w3.org/p3>.

If you would like to know more information about cookies and how they are used on the Internet then more information can be found at <http://www.w3.org/P3P/>.

**Disabling Cookies**  
If you do not wish Unanimis to place cookies on your computer, you can disable cookies through your internet browser. If you want to opt out of receiving customized interest-based advertising from Unanimis [click here](http://www.unanimis.co.uk/oba/).

Please keep in mind that you will still see as many ads, only they will not be based on your interests. 

_Unanimis follows a set of self-regulatory good practice principles implemented by the Interactive Advertising Bureau Europe.[Find out more](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/) about those recommendations and turn off interest-based advertising from all ad networks [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices)._

## The ad serving process

**Collection of anonymous information through ad serving technology and services**  
When an Internet user visits a website where one of our client’s advertisements or web beacons are placed using Unanimis’ ad serving technology and services, we collect and store information about the visit – namely, the user’s anonymous cookie ID, the specific ad posted on the site, and the time and place of delivery. If the user clicked on the ad, we collect and store that fact. We also collect information about how many times users view and click on our clients’ advertisements and whether or not a user visits specific pages of a client advertiser’s website (e.g. a registration page). We collect only a portion of the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses from users when we serve advertisements or web beacons on a website.

Sometimes clients will send us anonymous information they collected online during transactions so that we can provide targeted advertisements and analyze if our advertising has resulted in sales. In this process, the information that we receive is completely anonymous to Unanimis. This information relates to online transactions, including, but not limited to, the client-assigned user’s ID, transaction sales total, product ID, and other demographic data. Unanimis will also collect data on events that occur on a client’s website, such as when a user has applied for a loan. In these instances, Unanimis does not know the content of such a transaction or the identity of the user, merely that the event, a loan application, occurred. Unanimis does not receive any information from our clients in this process that would allow us to identify any individual.

**Use of anonymous information**  
The anonymous information that we collect is useful only to the specific advertisers who hire us to deliver ads, and only in the context of our selection of ad-content and our reporting of ad-effectiveness to our client. In order to assess an advertising campaign’s effectiveness, both Web and email based, we will report to our client our analysis of the anonymous data in a summarized format. On occasion, our clients ask us to send them, or their agents, our anonymous data that is collected on their specific website. In these situations, we send our anonymous data. We recommend that you visit our clients’ websites to review their privacy policies and contact them directly if you have questions about their information practices.

**Storage of anonymous information**  
This anonymous information relating to the delivery of advertising and tracking tags by Unanimis is stored securely within Unanimis data centers. Unanimis has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, including password controls.

Unanimis’ policy is to retain anonymous data for up to three years.

**Correcting anonymous information**  
Because we do not know the identities of persons associated with the anonymous data that we collect, we cannot give anyone access to or the ability to change this anonymous information.

**Collection and use of personally identifying information**  
The ad serving technology we provide enables our clients to track information relating to the advertisements that we serve and transactions that take place after a user has clicked on an advertisement. The information collected in this way may include personally identifying information, for example where a user has made a purchase from our client after clicking on one of their ads. We only collect personally identifiable information relating to users where our clients ask us to. Where we collect personally identifiable information through our ad-serving technology, we do so as a data processor – the advertiser (our client) is the relevant data controller and you should consult their privacy policy for details on how your personally identifiable information may be used.

**Our Right to Change This Policy**  
Unanimis reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. We will let you know at the top of this page the date it was last updated. To understand how your information will be used we encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you use this web site.
